Uh, you guys fire away.
Alright, how excited is she are you I
mean for the whole thing but especially
to be coming to the Saints?
Man, more than thankful more than
thankful for the opportunity and man, I
just can't can't wait to go down there
and put in some work with my boys man,
you know, ain't too far from Baton Rouge
man, I'm just an hour so you know, let's
do it man. Can't wait. Can't wait.
How much contact did you have with the
Saints leading up to this? How much how
much did you know they had an interest
in you? Man, like with all the coaches
and GMs man, I built a great
relationship man. I kind of always had
it in the back of my head that I was
going there. This is the only hat that
my parents bought today which is crazy
and
man, just love the facility and just
[laughter] love the love the connection
that I made with them boys and man, I
just can't wait to go to work man.
More than thankful more than proud man.
Was was the hat decision one because you
felt like that was the team you were
going to or was that your parents trying
to will it into existence? Man, honestly
I I asked them if they can get all 32
hats to my mom said that they only had
the Saints at the store they was at so
you know, we got the Saints and
>> [laughter]
>> hey man, dream come true right now.
>> Where are you right now? I'm I'm in
Nashville in my backyard man. The the
house is too crazy right now so had to
come outside get some air breathe a
little bit and be thankful. Thank God
man. Let's go.
Hey Barry, people think of you as as a
fast guy but you're more of a tell us
why you are a good wide receiver.
Cuz I can do anything you want me to do
coach if you want me to go in there and
block I'll go in there and block and get
a screen pass let's do it. I'll run
through somebody burn and somebody just
whatever you need to do as a receiver
man, I'm here to do and I'm doing it
with a smile on my face.
You know, a great teammate at the end of
the day and just a guy that's always
going to bring the energy and the vibes
to practice and games man. Let's do it.
Barry, were you a big fan of Rashid
Shaheed and those shoes you'd like to
fill? Man, of course man. He's a great
great returner and you know, man just
looking at you know, do what I need to
do man. Let's go.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm sorry Y'ALL. I'M SORRY.
HEY BARRY, ARE YOU A LITTLE SURPRISED
that Garrett Nussmeier hasn't heard his
name called yet? Man, man yeah but
man, man we just trusting God and man
Garrett's a great guy great quarterback
and you know, God God going to have a
time for him and man when it when it
when it come I'm going to be man, just
excited man. Let's do it. Let's do it.
Hey Barry, have you have you spent time
thinking about okay the
kick return at the NFL level is a little
different and how
you handle that how that you would
approach that with your game?
Man, honestly I feel like any any
special teams is a will to do it man. If
you want to do it you'll get get out
there and do it so man, there's nothing
to me this is something I've been doing
catching the ball taking it to the house
for 100 yards and celebrating with my
with my teammates man so I feel like it
ain't a difference to me. It's just a
will to do it and I want to do it and I
want to do it so it's going to get done.
What what makes for a good what makes
for a good returner?
Man, explosiveness and and honestly
fearless. That that's the biggest one
for me fearless being able to run
through the smoke and you know, keep
your head up chin high and you know,
whatever comes with it man just just
take it take it to the chin. Let's do
it.
Barry, you played
in the Senior Bowl. What was that like
and also there were a lot of Saints
assistant coaches there. Is that when
you started saying that maybe it could
be the Saints?
Man, it was just a great experience all
around just going going down there and
get some work in with the coaches and
just hearing hearing their point of view
of things and you know, trying to add my
my point of view and you know, we
working and just being coached up and
just been a been a lot of been around a
lot of great guys and you know,
competing and that's something I like to
do. I compete my tail off so you know,
just being invited to one of the best of
the best you know, doing my thing and
you know, having fun while doing I
always say something about having fun
cuz man, you just got to have fun with
this stuff man. So
man, Senior Bowl was a blessing great
experience.
Man, I'm just ready y'all. I'm sorry but
I'm so excited man. I'm ready. Let's do
it.
Barry, talk to your pro day though, you
know, maybe the transfer didn't go
exactly how you had hoped and just going
through a season like that to still hear
your name called just is that a weight
off your shoulders where are the
emotions right now?
Um, yes sir and I that's just a
testimony that's man, it's going to be
sunlight and it's going to be dark days
and regardless of how you may feel about
it that's life and life life's going to
keep going so
just being able to keep my best foot
forward and attacking each and every day
like it's my last and just out there
having fun and you know, finding
enjoying it again man. I wouldn't I
wouldn't I wouldn't do it again for the
world bro. Love them boys man. Love
them.
What do you think of all these offensive
weapons the Saints have come up with the
last few days? Man, let's do it. I'm
ready to work man. I'm ready to work.
I'm ready to work. I'm ready to work.
Let's do it. Come on.
Uh, Barry when it comes to kind of
adding an element on offense for New
Orleans, what do you think about your
ability as a yards after catch receiver?
That's something I've been doing since a
baby man.
It's just like I got a feel for the end
zone and I'm always looking to find the
end zone and that's whether it could be
a jet sweep a deep ball or a screen
slant whatever the case may be man. I'm
just looking to always score the ball
man.
Hey Barry, have you had a chance to
visit with Lane Kiffin down in Baton
Rouge since he's arrived?
Um, not really just visit with him but I
didn't I didn't come and watch a few
practice and I was training and stuff
when I was down there in BR but you
know, I just try to stay out their way
and you know, let them keep getting
better each and every day and you know,
I had some something to do I had a plan
of mine in my head so you know, I just
had to attack every day.
Thanks so much. Congratulations. Thanks
Barry.
Thanks Barry.
Thank you so much. Let's do it.